Mushfigur Alam

Bhuiyan



Profile

Date of Birth: 04/01/2001 Blood Group: B+

Languages: English, Bangla

Contact

Address:

10/C, Boshoti Housing, Borobagh, Mirpur

Section-2, Dhaka-1216

Phone:

+8801851742939

Email:

moshfiquralam@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/mushfiquralam-bhuiyan-8a857a1aa/

Awards & Honors

Edexcel Award for IGCSE - 2017 Daily Star Award for IGCSE - 2017

Strength

Leadership, Self-motivated, Communication, Fast-learner

Hobbies

Travelling, Learning new things, playing football

Summary

Leadership - oriented management, public management, has the ability to explain people with good words, has problem-solving abilities and also learn things quickly. Currently I am working as the General Secretary of JUKTI - the official club of CSE, IUB. I have good proficiency in English and Bangla and have good knowledge about programming language. I am currently a student of the department of Computer Science and Engineering in Independent University, Bangladesh. I am keen to get new experiences in the real world.

Education

Bachelor of Science – 2020 - Present **Independent University, Bangladesh (IUB)**

Major: Computer Science and Engineering

CGPA: 3.76

International Advanced Level (IAL) – 2018 - 2019 British Council, Dhaka

Subjects: Physics, Chemistry, Mathematics

Grades: 1A, 2Bs

IGCSE – 2017 - 2018 British Council, Dhaka Grades: 5A*s, 3As, 1B

Experience

General Secretary - 06/2021 - Present

JUKTI - Official Club of CSE. IUB

- Plan and manage events successfullly
- Represent the club in other platforms

Content Assistant (Freelancer) – 12/2021 – 04/2022

Foodpanda, Bangladesh

• Create, edit, delete, categorize the contents of the database.

Teaching Assistant – 02/2017 – 11/2018 **Academia School Dhaka**, Lalmatia, Dhaka, Bangladesh

Skill Highlights

- C++
- SQL
- Management

- Problem Solving
- Team Work
- Service-focused

Projects

Microprocessor, Interfacing and Assembly Language – CSE216

Project on "IoT based Irrigation Monitoring and Control System" Report on the project in IEEE format

Database Management System - CSE303

Project on "Air quality management system" using sql, python, django Report on analysis and design of "Air quality management system"

Electrical Circuit Analysis - CSE104

IEEE Term Paper - The development of infrared sensor and its application